Attention, brothers! Missing this treasure month event will result in a direct loss of 100 million.
In the treasure map just released by the official, there are twelve treasure points hidden in Dam Zero.
I've already pulled it out for my brothers. It is recommended to take a screenshot and save it directly. Once the event starts, rush directly!
Treasure No. 1 is located in the underground excavation area of the dam in the middle of the map, roughly at this location.
Treasure No. 2 is located near the watchtower below the cement factory, and will most likely be placed on this brick.
Treasure No. 3 is located in the pipe behind the uniform, near the three-mission Easter egg crate on the third floor.
Treasure No. 4 is located at the entrance of the visitor center in the lower right corner of the map.
There is a high probability that it will be painted near the white container. Treasure point No. 5 is located near the river beach.
It is very likely that it will be painted on the red container or on the ground. Treasure No. 6 is located on the hillside below the wild camp.
There is a high probability that it will be brushed on this box. Treasure No. 7 is located between the top of the dam and the mountainside maintenance station.
There is a high probability that it will be painted on the red container. Treasure No. 8 is located near the container in the Administration Building.
There is a high probability that it will be refreshed on the container. Treasure No. 9 is located at the top of the dam.
Treasure No. 10 is located at the foot of the mountain on the right side of the camp, and will most likely be found in the basement room.
Treasure No. 11 is located near the construction site on the left side outside the Administration West Building.
Most likely it will appear at the entrance to the basement or on a box next to it.
Treasure point No. 12 is located in the cement factory, near the entrance of the underground passage.
The above is the approximate location of the No. 0 Dam treasure.
However, the specific refresh mechanism will not be known until the event goes online. I will be there for testing as soon as possible.
The revised coordinates will be updated at that time. Brothers who find it useful, don't forget to click and follow.
See you in the next video!